<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Beard Care for Extreme Conditions]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Beard Care for Extreme Conditions]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/polarbeards/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 14:04:18 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/polarbeards/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Polarbeards]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Polarbeards</h1><p>The start of Polar Beards technically goes back over two years ago, when we got tired of trying beard oils that didn’t work well enough for us. Our vision was to find the ultimate blend of oils, that manages to keep our beards nourished and moisturized, as well as fight the inevitable dryness of the skin underneath the beard. Other beard oils on the market just didn’t do the trick in extreme conditions, such as -30 Celsius winters in Lapland, when the air is very dry.

We experimented with over a hundred different blends and ratios until we were finally pleased with our product. The fact that we wanted to include only organic oils and stay away from nut derived oils, didn’t make the task any easier.

Because this started simply as a project to create the perfect beard oil for ourselves, instead of a commercial one, we never acquired big and heavy equipment for mass production. Our oils are still mixed in very small batches to ensure the exactness of the ratios and the overall quality of the product, and we intend to keep it that way.

Lastly, we tested our beard oil against the placebo effect by matching it up with over 30 of the most popular beard oils available on the market. You should understand that all beard oils strive to take care of your beard and the skin underneath it. Most of them do OK for a short period of time, a few could be described as good and some even make it worse.

We can honestly and proudly say we feel the Polar Beards Beard Oil knocked even the best and the priciest oils easily off the table. What we took into consideration was how fast it absorbs, the duration of the effect and obviously how well it works.

We managed to outperform every single beard oil we tested, in all of the categories.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ee775747834cb0e920f895d655ebc03e05c91244.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/polarbeards/polarbeards/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">df160925-9bef-4656-a14a-32bf0fbd3e5d</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 13:45:09 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[KLASSINEN PARRANAJO
PARAS TAPA AJAA PARTA. EDELLEEN.]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>KLASSINEN PARRANAJO
PARAS TAPA AJAA PARTA. EDELLEEN.</h1><p>Vanha kunnon klassinen parranajo on monellakin tapaa ylivertainen verrattuna moniterähöyliin ja partakoneisiin. Hyötyihin kuuluu mm. ajon tarkkuus, ihon ärsytyksen minimointi ja ennen kaikkea koko parranajotavan tyylikkyys ja mukavuus. Kun varaat parranajolle vähän enemmän aikaa ja teet sen kunnolla alusta loppuun, muuttuu koko rutiini pakollisesta pahasta odotetuksi päivän kohokohdaksi.

Koko hyöty ei suinkaan tule ainoastaan paremman höylän takia, vaikka se varmasti suurin yksittäinen faktori onkin. Kunnon partasaippua ja huolellinen valmistelu ja ajo ovat myös tärkeitä hyvän parranajokokemuksen saavuttamiseksi.

Klassista parranajoa voi myös harrastaa ihan perinteisellä partaveitsellä, shavetella, tai vaikka kirveellä, mutta me olemme valinneet välineeksemme vanhan liiton partahöylän (Safety Razor), sen tyylikkyyden ja aloittelijaystävällisyyden vuoksi.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/52c9dd32-71dd-4023-97d1-f277a9d833da.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/polarbeards/klassinen-parranajo-paras-tapa-ajaa-parta-edelleen/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">9294e8d1-3f50-49e8-826b-88a9463e16d1</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 14:03:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beard Oil Green]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Beard Oil Green</h1><p>Bring out the woodsman in you. This beard oil has been cultivated by months of research and made with only the finest natural blends of oils. Simply put, it is the best beard oil on the market. The Beardbrand beard oil is designed to be very lightweight and will help keep your beard conditioned and shiny. Because it’s a lightweight blend, it won’t weigh down your beard or feel greasy.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/8da63842fbdea4c098d236ca9f1d022c7db4d531.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/polarbeards/beard-oil-green/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">84478641-94f9-4060-b747-28cb61c75e38</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 13:42:38 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beard Oil Blue]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Beard Oil Blue</h1><p>Bring out the woodsman in you. This beard oil has been cultivated by months of research and made with only the finest natural blends of oils. Simply put, it is the best beard oil on the market. The Beardbrand beard oil is designed to be very lightweight and will help keep your beard conditioned and shiny. Because it’s a lightweight blend, it won’t weigh down your beard or feel greasy.</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/0827d8387f4f410fa16e2e488d38b0ee7f649820.png"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/polarbeards/beard-oil-blue/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a2714865-a9c8-4662-99b1-ebef76cac25e</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 13:42:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>